

# ESTEBAN BENABARRE FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Fullstack Developer, currently studying to become a Software engineer.

Expert in capital markets with an extensive knowledge in customer service. I consider important to continuously grow and develop my skills exploring outside my comfort zone. I love teamwork and to contribute with my knowledge when I see someone needs it.

My main goal is to grow in the field of software development through continuous studying, practice and participation in blockchain and smart contract related projects, taking advantage of my experience acquired in other areas.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering

Tech University | Mar 2022 - In progress

# SmartContract - Solidity

EducaciónIT, Jul 2022 - In progress

· Smart contract developer with Solidity

## Full Stack Developer MERN

Coderhouse | May 2021 - In progress

• MongoDB, Express, ReactJS y NodeJS.

#### Capital Markets Expert

Universidad Tec. Nacional | May 2021 - Nov 2021

• MongoDB, Express, ReactJS y NodeJS.

#### Electromechanical Technician

Inst. Dr. Juan Segundo Fernandez | 2001 - 2007

 Perform preventive, predictive and corrective maintenance program of facilities and equipment.

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- ★ Master Service Advisor Toyota Argentina.
- ★ Certified Service Advisor Mercedes Benz.

## TOOLS AND LANGUAGES

**5** HTML

**∃** CSS

Js Javascript

node Node JS

React JS

MONGO

MYSQL

Python

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Web Developer, Freelance

Becode | Mar2022 - actually

 Freelance web programmer, responsive web page design with Javascript, React and NextJS.

### Service Advisor Sr.

Besten Mercedes Benz | Mar 2018 - Oct 2021

 In charge of commercial attention, sale of intangibles, technical advice. Process design and management. Planning and organization of activities. Management of complaints and administrative processes.

#### Workshop Manager

TOYOTA Sarthou | Abr 2017 - Mar 2018

 Workshop manager, process control, group planning, task scheduling. Work team coordination.

## Service Advisor Ssr.

TOYOTA Sarthou | Jan 2012 - Abr 2017

• Commercial service, sale of intangible assets, technical advice.

# LANGUAGES

- ★ English Upper Intermediate
- \* Spanish Native

## CONTACT ME AT

+54 11 5634 0008

https://github.com/Bena90

https://www.linkedin.com/in/esteban-benabarre/

https://www.esteban-benabarre.com

@ esteban.benabarre@gmail.com

San Isidro, Buenos Aires, Argentina